This is the time known as the Great Pirate Era.
A countless array of pirates go to battle across the seas in search of the One Piece,
the legendary treasure left behind by Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned to rubber after eating the gum gum fruit,
set sail to become the next King of the Pirates.
As Luffy and his crew conquer numerous obstacles,
they capture the unwanted attention of the world government,
which will use any means necessary to stop them.
Now this is sight!
Can't wait to see what kind of adventure's up next!
With a charted course awash in danger and intrigue,
the crew will cut a path across the Grand Line to the New World.
The Navy triumphed in the War of the Best,
and Luffy, unable to save his brother Ace, fell into despair.
But this is a story from another time,
ten years ago in the East Blue,
when the brothers ran wild with dreams of a world full of adventure.
To live up to the promise, departures of their own.
The World Nobles' visit to the Goa Kingdom has come and gone.
But another visitor lingers.
At a small village in the East Blue,
a group of aspiring swordsmen chat about the strange encounter.
Did you see that weird guy with the big head?
Yeah, his face was totally crazy too!
I bet he needs that giant ship to fit his giant head!
580...
581...
582...
583...
584...
You certainly kept me waiting!
What could possibly be more important than me?
Sorry!
Goodness, is that...
Someone get help!
This doesn't look good.
Let's prepare treatment!
Roger!
Honestly, what in the world have you been up to all day?
I was watching the ceremony they held for the World Noble.
Ah! One, that's some risky business, and two, why didn't you take me?
Because you would attract too much attention, obviously.
Ah! Could it be I'm too fabulous?
At any rate, we've tarried for long enough. We've got business to attend to.
Do we have supplies?
The training hall at the village gave us just enough food for now.
Very well.
Set sail. We're heading back to Baltico.
A short time later, in the nearby Goa Kingdom...
Ah! Finally, some junk!
Although the fire raised Gray Terminal and its people to the ground...
Another sea of trash and another sea of scavengers appeared.
You're in for it this time! Here it goes!
Now go, go!
Pistons!
Are you kidding me? You still suck butt.
It doesn't matter how hard you punch if you can't hit anything.
I told you, rubber's a crappy power. It's no good for fighting.
Shut up! You're dumb!
You're the dumb one! I'm honest, that's all!
I'm trying to save you from falling on your stupid rubber ass all day!
You're just jealous because you can't do awesome stuff like me!
All you've got are jerk powers and I'm working on all kinds of cool moves!
Luffy, that was great!
Man, that punch of yours flies further and further every day!
Come on! If you go easy on him, he'll get a big head!
I got stronger today and I'm going to be even stronger tomorrow!
Right, Sabu?
Huh?
Sabu was a nice brother, not like you.
You're trying to say it'd be better if I died, aren't you?
I didn't say anything like that!
Yeah, but that's what you meant, isn't it?
Ah! That's what I'm talking about!
Sabu would never hit me, you jerk!
So what?
Be nice to your brother, that's what!
Nuh-ah!
Ow!
Huh?
I'm hereby establishing my own country!
He's doing what now?
Me too!
What are you little idiots up to now?
We need to be strong enough to live on our own!
You're from the Dadan kingdom, by the way!
We still need to use your bath, though!
Hmm.
Ace!
This one is way too big!
I need your help!
You?
The mighty King Luffy needs help?
Here goes!
No!
Hey, it's the Dawn Kingdom!
We need help!
Luffy got hurt!
He's in trouble!
Magra, hurry up!
This is bad!
Okay, Ace. Hurry, bring him inside!
Okay, wow.
It's a good thing you brought him here when you did.
Also, if this cut had been any deeper,
he probably would have died on the spot.
I hate to say it, but this is no good with only two of you.
It's all my fault.
I knew better.
Even if you're a captain,
fighting alone doesn't make you any stronger.
I'm still no good.
I'm still not good enough.
No, no.
I'm sorry, Luffy.
I let you down.
Guys, come see!
Makino came to visit, and she brought booze!
You want to know how to properly say thank you?
Mm-hmm.
And what's this about paying respects?
As a pirate and as Luffy's big brother,
I need to pay my respects to this Shanks guy.
Luffy says he owes the man his life,
so it's kind of the least I can do.
Uh...
Got something to say to me?!
Sorry, sorry.
Okay, I think I can give you some tips.
For starters, after a meal...
It's a dining dish!
Come back!
Wait a sec, we almost forgot.
Gotta pay respect.
Oops!
Yeah, you're right!
Oh?
Thank you for the meal, sir.
Thank you for the meal, sir!
Ah!
Keep your thanks!
Are you brats gonna pay me or what?!
I'm not losing the day!
No way!
Ah!
Something higher!
Uh...
All right!
Now for some bear meat stew.
These obscure fries.
Mechanical человек.
Mechanical cheese.
Unbowhead.
We'll be right back.
Take care, Ace. See ya!
Yeah! See you soon! Keep training hard!
Just give me three years, and before you know it, my wanted poster's gonna be everywhere you go!
Kick some ass! Bon voyage!
Don't catch a cold out there!
Look for me in the papers. It won't take long, okay?
The world did not know that the son of Gold Roger had grown up in secret.
Nor did they know that he set sail that day, determined to make a name of his own.
Yes, that's it, huh?
Honestly, if Garp were here, think of what he'd say.
I'm gonna need you to raise this baby for me.
What? Why? Is it even yours?
So there you are, boss.
Hey, believe it or not, Ace is gone.
That's so. Well, one last brat to worry about, though I'm sure Garp will give me hell for it.
Kid left and he's still causing me trouble.
Oh, I almost forgot. There's a message he asked us to give to you.
Yeah? Why should I care? He probably just wants to tell me my feet smell or something.
He said, thank you for taking care of me.
How could you do that to me, you beast?
What's wrong, boss? You're not crying, are you?
If you don't shut up, I'll make you cry!
Three more years, that's the rule.
Now go, go, pick up!
So close! I just need a little more!
You almost got it now, Luffy.
Bend your legs a little and aim straight ahead.
Now come, come!
Pissed off!
Gah!
Gotta keep getting stronger!
Hang on, Ace!
I'm coming for you!
Luffy!
You gotta see the paper! Look!
Oh, what's up?
It's just like he said!
Whoa, you're right! Ace made the news!
He's got a ship and a crew and everything!
Oh, man! I'm so jealous!
Wow!
But I'm gonna do even better!
Hey, you guys!
I'm leaving now! You're not gonna see me off?
Hey!
Use your head for once!
The mayor and Makino wouldn't mind us stopping by, but as for everyone else in Windmill Village, we'd probably scare the pants right off him!
I don't know!
Ugh, don't make it awkward! Just go already!
Okay!
Okay. Well, goodbye, you guys! Thanks for everything! I'm sure gonna miss you!
Oh, now don't say that! You're gonna make us blush!
Well, bye! Take it easy!
I will! You guys too, okay?
Oh, one last thing!
Huh?
Don, I still think mountain bandits are super lame!
Shut up and leave, dammit!
But you guys, you're great!
It's not enough to ruin my life! Now you gotta break my heart, too!
You're awful, I tell you! All of you are good for nothing!
Sorry I made you cry!
Shut up or I'll make you cry!
Now to Windmill Village on Dawn Island at the edge of the Goa Kingdom!
No offense, but why don't you take my old fishing boat instead, Luffy?
That thing is gonna sink as soon as you get out to sea!
That's too small, even for you!
I wanna start small, but I'll get a real big one soon! Don't worry!
Sabo!
Here I go!
No! Watch out for me out there, okay?
Sabo was first, and Ace was second!
I may be the last to go, but I'm gonna be the best!
I'm coming for you, Ace!
And all my special moves work now, too!
Why are you talking to yourself?
Is this some kind of pirate ritual I don't get?
No, it's a challenge to my brother, Ace!
Ace? Who is that?
I don't know.
Okay, I'm going for real now!
I knew this day would come, but I'm still a bit sad.
I'll sure miss him.
Oh, sad as fright, like the world needs another pirate.
Perfect weather today!
Hey, lookie me!
Oh, no!
Hey, pal. It's been a while, huh?
This won't play out like last time. I've been practicing this move for ten whole years!
This won't play out like last time! I've been practicing this move for ten whole years!
Now, Gon-Gon!
Pistol!
No!
Hmph. Been waiting a long time to do that.
Yeah!
He just took out that sea monster in one punch.
I gotta admit, I'm proud.
First, I need a crew. About ten people should be enough.
After that, pirate flag!
Alright! Let's get going!
Someday I'm gonna be...
King of the Pirates!
But time has not been kind.
And after the death of Ace, Luffy's optimism from that day is nowhere in sight.
Please! Luffy!
Me! King of the Pirates!
What a joke!
Look at me!
I'm useless!
I'm too weak!
Garp returns from the war and visits Luffy's hometown, only to receive a cold welcome from
the Don.
Meanwhile, Luffy is still inconsolable after the death of his brother.
As Jinbei watches over him, desperate to ease his friend's suffering, he recalls something
that Ace once said.
On the next, One Piece!
I wanna see them!
Luffy's mournful cry!
I'm gonna be king of the pirates!